Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - April 1974
    - Kristine M. Molt, Conference Coordinator, 740409 (Box 15)
    - Bagpipers play at Willard Straight, 740410 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes, 740411 (Box 15)
    - ASA 50 (PTX in Beutler's) campus scenes, 740412 (Box 15)
    - Farrier with cow, Vet School, 740413 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes, 740414 (Box 15)
    - Risley prepares for the fair, 740415 (Box 15)
    - Red Tide, 740416 (Box 15)
    - Wood's Hole by Marty Stiles R1-7, 740417 (Box 15)
    - Risley Medieval fair, R1-4, 740418 (Box 15)
    - Ben Bluitt, Head Basketball coach, 740419 (Box 15)
    - Open House, Veterinary College, 740420 (Box 15)
  - May 1974
    - Frederic W. Scott, Director, Feline Research Laboratory, 740501 (Box 15)
    - New Trees on Arts Quad, 740502 (Box 15)
    - Views from Multicategorical Bldg., 740503 (Box 15)
    - Southeast Asia Students, 740504 (Box 15)
    - Interiors-Chem Research Lab r1-Jerry Edelstein, 740505 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 740506 (Box 15)
    - Irving Younger, Law School and Model Trains, 740507 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes R1, 2 Cornell Lacrosse R3- by Jerry, 740508 (Box 15)
    - New Trees on Arts Quad, 740509 (Box 15)
    - Marylynn Salmon, 740510 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 740511 (Box 15)
    - Robert S. Pasley, Prof. Of Law, 740512 (Box 15)
    - Equine Research Park, 740513 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 740514 (Box 15)
    - Doug Dunnan '77 on Baldwin Stairway R1, 2 Sol-Color, 740515 (Box 15)
    - Baker Labs, 740516 (Box 15)
    - John James Deshon '08, former Baseball Player at Cornell, 740517 (Box 15)
  - June 1974
    - ROTC Commissioning, 740601 (Box 15)
    - Employee degree Program, 740602 (Box 15)
    - Spencer T. Olin Chemical research Lab Dedication, 740603 (Box 15)
    - Commencement, 740604 (Box 15)
    - Oat tree Table presented to Olins, 740605 (Box 15)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 740606 (Box 15)
    - Women's Sailing, 740607 (Box 15)
    - Latin Class taught by Cornell students to 3rd grade, Belle Sherman, 740608 (Box 15)
    - Robert A. Plane, Prof. Chemistry, Former Provost at Surprise Party, 740609 (Box 15)
    - Barton Scoreboard, 740610 (Box 15)
    - President's Councillors '74--Jose, 740611 (Box 15)
    - Herb Garden Dedication, 740612 (Box 15)
    - Reunion (Vet College on R-15), 740613 (Box 15)
    - I & LR Personnel, 740614 (Box 15)
    - Vet College Multi-cat Dedication, 740615 (Box 15)
  - July 1974
    - Interiors of Library, Campus Store, Sage Dining-Jose, 740701 (Box 15)
    - Bailey Hall, Campus Store, Clark Hall, McGraw Tower, Sage Graduate Center, Uris Hall, Willard-Straight, Caldwell Hall, Comstock Hall, Mann Library, Space Sciences Building--Jose, 740702
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Students eating, talking inside Willard straight, Walking in rain--Jose, 740703 (Box 15)
    - Comm. Arts Center, Foundry, anabel Taylor, Myron taylor--Jose, 740704 (Box 15)
    - Ag Quad-Caldwell Hall, Comstock Hall, Emerson Hall, Fernow Hall, Mann Library, Plant Sciences Building, Roberts Hall, Warren Hall--Jose, 740705
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - West Campus-Baker tower, Boldt Hall, Class of '22 Hall, McGraw Tower, Noyes Center, Risley--Jose, 740706 (Box 15)
    - Shots from Agronomy Building, Campus Scenes, Barton Hall, Bruckner Lab, Emerson Hall, Lua A. Minns Garden, Rice Hall--Jose, 740707
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Barton Hall, Lynah Rink, Schoellkopf Hall, Statler Hall & Auditorium, Teagle Hall--Jose, 740708 (Box 15)
    - Engineering Quad-Hollister, Kimball, Phillips, Upson, Ward Lab West Campus Housing-Lyon Hall, McFaddin Hall, Baker Towers--Jose, 740709
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - James Hutton, Kappa Alpha Prof. Of the Classics, Emeritus, 740710 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes: sage Chapel, Campus Store, W. Straight Patio--Jose, 740711 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes:Outdoor Class, North Campus Union, Barnes Hall--Jose, 740712 (Box 15)
    - North Campus Union, Clara Dickson, Mary Donlon, Observatory, Kids, Spencer T. Olin Chemistry Research Laboratory--Jose, 740713
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Arecibo, R1-13--Russ, 740714 (Box 15)
    - Thomas A. Sokol, Music Professor, Conducts Choir--Jose, 740715 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes, 740716 (Box 15)
    - President Corson lectures on photography to summer EVA students, 740717 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes (from Olin Library roof), 740718 (Box 15)
    - (from Olin Chemistry Research Laboratory roof), " (Box 15)
    - Cornell Alumni University, 740719 (Box 15)
    - Summer Campus scenes, 740720 (Box 15)
    - Barnes Hall, Uris Library Interiors, " (Box 15)
    - Weinhold Chilled Water Plant, Noyes Lodge, Van Rensselaer Hall, Plant Science Bldg., Warren Hall, Helen Newman--Jose, 740721
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Veterinary Research Tower, Stocking Hall, Wing Hall, Riley-Robb Hall, Judging Pavillion, Kenneth Post Lab, U.S. Plant, Soil & Nutrition Lab, Morrison Hall, Virology & Nematology Lab--Jose, 740722
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Floyd R. Newman Lab, Clark Hall, Baker Labs, Olin Chemistry Research Lab, Bailey Hall, 740723 (Box 15)
    - Power Plant, Balch Dorm, Risley Dorm, " (Box 15)
    - Schurman Hall, Scaffolding at Sage Graduate Center--Jose, 740724 (Box 15)
    - Cutting down elm trees on Arts Quad, repairing Olin Library roof--Jose, 740725 (Box 15)
    - Pottery-making, German-made magnet taken to Synchrotron, + Sol's Crowded Office, 740726 (Box 15)
  - August 1974
    - Campus Scenes: Engineering Exteriors--Jose, 740801 (Box 15)
    - Industrial & Labor Relations Exteriors--Jose, 740802 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Catering Reception--Jose, 740803 (Box 15)
    - International Drum & Bugle Corps Competition @ Schoellkopf Field, 740804 (Box 15)
    - Egg and Campus Scenes, 740805 (Box 15)
    - Freshmen Arrival & Corson speaks to parents, 740806 (Box 15)
    - Gary Smith, Veterans Administration Advisor, 740807 (Box 15)
    - Main Line, Drug Counseling Center, 740808 (Box 15)
    - Registration & Freshmen Arrival, 740809 (Box 15)
    - Microfilming old newspapers, 740810 (Box 15)
  - September 1974
    - Campus Scenes, 740901 (Box 15)
    - NYS Governor Malcolm Wilson tours Vet College Research Tower, 740902 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 740903 (Box 15)
    - Bryant Robey, Director, Public Information, Thomas R. Rogers, Director Academic Funding, Joseph Leeming, Asst. Director, Radio-TV, Public Information, 740904
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Equitation Class, 740905 (Box 15)
    - David C. Knapp, Provost; W. Don Cooke, Former Acting Provost; Campus Scenes, 740906 (Box 15)
    - Stumping for the Heart Fund, Tim Ray, Prof. Ernest F. Schaufler, Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture & Joanne Gruttadaurio with Talking Plastic Plant, 740907
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Robert H. Wasserman, Prof. Of Physical Biology, Lennart P. Krook, Prof. Of Veterinary Pathology, 740908 (Box 15)
    - Opening Night at "Directions in Afro-American Art", an exhibit at H.F. Johnson Museum, 740909 (Box 15)
    - WHCU radio antenna comes down, 740910 (Box 15)
    - H. F. Johnson Museum at night--Jerry Edelstein '77, 740911 (Box 15)
    - Reception for new faculty with President Corson in Johnson Museum Lobby, 740912 (Box 15)
    - United Fund Kick-off, 740913 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 740914 (Box 15)
    - Joel Gajardo, a staff associate to C.U. Committee on U.S.-Latin American Relations, 740915 (Box 15)
    - Football Clinic for Kids Punt, Pass & Kick, 740917 (Box 15)
    - Women's Field Hockey, 740918 (Box 15)
    - Apple harvest at Cornell Orchard, 740919 (Box 15)
  - October 1974
    - Kimono added to Cornell Costume Collection, 741001 (Box 15)
    - Fall-In, 741002 (Box 15)
    - Rugby, 741003 (Box 15)
    - Sciences-Humanities Symposium, 741004 (Box 15)
    - Judo, 741005 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs Bucknell football--Andy Lauterback '76, 741006 (Box 15)
    - Fall In--Andy Lauterback '76, 741007 (Box 15)
    - Sage Chapel Interiors, 741008 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs U. of Penn. Football, 741009 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes--Jerry Edelstein '77, 741010 (Box 15)
    - Modern Dance Class, 741011 (Box 15)
    - Jack Henion, Sr. Research Assoc. & Mass Spectrometer, 741012 (Box 15)
    - Trustee Council Meeting, 741013 (Box 15)
    - Basketball Practice with new coach, Ben Bluitt, 741014 (Box 15)
    - Women's Gymnastics, 741015 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs Yale Soccer, 741016 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs Yale Football, 741017 (Box 15)
    - WBNG-TV films Thomas W. Leavitt, Director, H.F. Johnson Museum of Art, 741018 (Box 15)
    - International Students' Dinner, 741019 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs Yale Crosscountry, 741020 (Box 15)
    - Homecoming (Dinner), 741021 (Box 15)
    - Donald P. Greenberg, Director, Computer Graphics Program, 741022 (Box 15)
    - N.Y.S. College of Veterinary Medicine, 741023 (Box 15)
  - November 1974
    - Industrial & Labor Relations Staff & Some Faculty (Profs. Trice & Hammer), 741101 (Box 15)
    - Game Farm Rededication, 741102 (Box 15)
    - Women's Volleyball, 741103 (Box 15)
    - Miron Benvenistri, Israel Scholar-In-residence lectures on Jerusalem--Sol, 741104 (Box 15)
    - Stimson Hall Renovations, 741105 (Box 15)
    - Ben Bluitt, Basketball Coach with staff, 741106 (Box 15)
    - Budget Press Conference, 741107 (Box 15)
    - Mail Service, 741108 (Box 15)
    - Teepee over campus store, 741109 (Box 15)
    - Turkeys, 741110 (Box 15)
    - Statuette-, 741111 (Box 15)
    - Risley Theatre Construction, 741112 (Box 15)
    - Students Protesting Proposed Tuition Hike, 741113 (Box 15)
    - Stan Reaves, Coordinator, WHCU's Black Affairs programming, 741114 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 741115 (Box 15)
    - Bosendorfer Imperial Piano, 741116 (Box 15)
  - December 1974
    - Cornell vs. York U. Hockey--Randy Shew, 741201 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs Dartmouth football, 741202 (Box 15)
    - Human ecology Class--special for the NY Times--Sol, 741203 (Box 15)
    - Xmas Carolers at President Dale R. Corson's office, 741204 (Box 15)
    - Profesor Hans A. Bethe's Champagne Retirement Party, 741205 (Box 15)
    - Xmas Concert in Sage Chapel, 741206 (Box 15)
    - Andrew D. White Statue in Santa Claus attire, 741207 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes--Andy Lauterback '76, 741208 (Box 15)
    - Heat exchanger implanted in calf at NYS Veterinary College--Connie Bart, 741209 (Box 15)
  - January 1975
    - Campus snow scenes, 750101 (Box 15)
    - "Westward"-100ft. Sailing & research vessel for "SEAGOING APPRENTICESHIP", 750102 (Box 15)
    - Women's 24 Hour Relay Team, 750103 (Box 15)
    - Public Skating at Lynah Rink, 750104 (Box 15)
    - Vet School Alumni Present Portrait of former Dean Poppensiek to the Vet College at Annual Conference for Veterinarians Banquet, 750105
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Registration, 750106 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Columbia in Fencing and Basketball--Sol, 750107 (Box 15)
    - George Seifert, Head Football Coach, 750108 (Box 15)
    - Student Composers with Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, 750109 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Princeton Hockey--Sol, 75010 (Box 15)
  - February 1975
    - Bust of Peter J. W. Debye, Former Professor of Chemistry, 750201 (Box 15)
    - Japanese Noh Dancer--copy neg., 750202 (Box 15)
    - Stimson Hall Renovations-Biology Center, 750203 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Harvard Wrestling, 750204 (Box 15)
    - Heating Plant Interiors & Smoke Stacks, 750205 (Box 15)
    - Campus snow scenes, 750206 (Box 15)
    - Mountaineering Class rappels at Schoellkopf Stadium; Gertrude Conklin, Custodian, 750207 (Box 15)
    - Vance A. Christian, Professor, Hotel School [Missing], 750208 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Brown Basketball, 750209 (Box 15)
    - Robert A. Hall, Jr., Professor of Linguistics, 750210 (Box 15)
    - Gertrude Conklin, Custodian; Models of Leonardo da Vinci's inventions displayed at Willard Straight, 750211 (Box 15)
    - David Borden, Composer/Pianist, 750212 (Box 15)
    - Women's Swimming-CU vs. Cortland & Bucknell, 750213 (Box 15)
    - Public Bowling at Helen Newman Hall, 750214 (Box 15)
    - DES Pill, 750215 (Box 15)
    - Visual Services Print Collage, 750216 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Heating Plant Exteriors (Town Trucks being loaded with heating plant ashes for recycling), 750217 (Box 15)
    - Women's Bowling-Cornell vs. Brockport; Eleanor H. Jorden, Professor of Linguistics and Director, FALCON/Japanese Program, and W. John McCoy, Associate Professor, Linguistics, 750218
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Russ Hamilton, Photo Editor and Sol Goldberg, Director, Visual Services, 750219 (Box 15)
    - Robert R. Ellis, Technician, Department of Geological Sciences, with mobile seismic reflection system, 750220 (Box 15)
    - Swimming-Cornell vs. Dartmouth, 750221 (Box 15)
    - Russ Hamilton, Photo Editor, Visual Services, lectures on photography to Prof. Chet Freeman's students at Communication Arts Center, 750222
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
  - March 1975
    - HEPS, 750301 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Boston University Hockey, 750302 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Univ. of Pennsylvania Hockey, 750303 (Box 15)
    - Rosita Moreno & Ray Millman, B & PA students, assist in preparation of income tax forms, 750304 (Box 15)
    - Dave Law, graduate student, working in Electrical Engineering Dept.'s Crystal Lab, 750305 (Box 15)
    - Quebec donates 400+ books to Cornell Hedrik Edelman, Asst. Director of Cornall's University Libraries, 750306 (Box 15)
    - George Peter, First Employee Trustee, Research Engineer, Radio Astronomy Lab, 750307 (Box 15)
    - Student/faculty social hour sponsored by Robert K. Kauffman '22 at Andrew D. White House, 750308 (Box 15)
    - Dr. Mary Smith and Vet School Ambulatory Clinic, 750309 (Box 15)
    - F. W. Olin Mementoes in University Archives Department, 750310 (Box 15)
    - Portrait of Mrs. Frank Gannett, 750311 (Box 15)
    - Portrait of Frank Gannett, " (Box 15)
    - Benjamin Nichols, Professor, Electrical Engineering, Speaker of Sixth Senate, 750312 (Box 15)
    - North Campus Union Craftshop, 750313 (Box 15)
    - Sornell savoyards lower sets down south staircase of Barton Hall, 750314 (Box 15)
    - Ivy Gymnastics Championship, 750315 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Savoyards rehearse "Trial by Jury", 750316 (Box 15)
    - Huddi Walsh '78, woman swimming star, and coach Bill Barton, 750317 (Box 15)
    - St. Patrick's Day Antics including the Green Dragon, 750318 (Box 15)
    - Diane Ackerman, Graduate Fellow in Humanities, Science & Technology, 750319 (Box 15)
    - Water Filter Plant (Cornell Univ.), 750320 (Box 15)
    - Copy Negatives of (2) 35mm color transparencies of chickadee-by John Dunning and Prof. Peter P. Kellogg--by Sol Goldberg, 750321
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Campus Store Courtyard Covered, 750322 (Box 15)
    - Copy negative of Equine Research Park #741023 R 5-24 after airbrushing, 750323 (Box 15)
  - April 1975
    - Copy negative of lobster; campus store courtyard roof; "Song of the Vowels"- Lipschitz sculpture; Uris Library interiors, 750401
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Trustee Robert S. Hatfield at I & LR, 750402 (Box 15)
    - Scotch tape & McGraw tower, 750403 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes, Campus store courtyard roof, Javanese shadow puppets, tri-critical opalescents, 750404 (Box 15)
    - James Hoffa at Industrial & Labor Relations, 750405 (Box 15)
    - Floyd O'Grady, Custodian of Sage Chapel and Campus Scenes, 750406 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse Practice, 750407 (Box 15)
    - Jack Schrager, '75, Essay Winner, 750408 (Box 15)
    - Raoul A. Sudre, Head Fencing Coach; Ken Torino, NCAA Epee Fencer of the Year; Nilo Otero, All-American; Jean-Jacques Gillet, Asst. Fencing Coach, 750409
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Pencil Stubs, 750410 (Box 15)
    - Welcome Ceremonies for Chinese Solid State Physicists, 750411 (Box 15)
    - Harry Caplan, Goldwin Smith Professor of the Classical Languages & Literature-Emeritus, 750412 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Ithaca College baseball, 750413 (Box 15)
    - Hotel School, 750414 (Box 15)
    - Women's Synchronized Swimming & Campus Scenes (Jerry Edelstein), 750415 (Box 15)
    - Biological Sciences, 750416 (Box 15)
    - Joggers (80 yr. Old man with boy), 750417 (Box 15)
    - University Orchestra (Sol), 750418 (Box 15)
    - Cornell vs. Johns Hopkins Lacrosse, 750419 (Box 15)
    - Parachute Jumping, 750420 (Box 15)
    - Richard A. Scheff "75, winner of Oxford Univ. Scholarship, 750421 (Box 15)
    - COSEP Rally & March, 750422 (Box 15)
    - Vet College Open House, 750423 (Box 15)
    - Risley Fair Rehersal; "Stress-skin roof" theatre, 750424 (Box 15)
    - Sage Chapel Interiors and burial vaults, 750425 (Box 15)
    - Mt. Pleasant Observatory, 750426 (Box 15)
    - Crew (Sol), 750427 (Box 15)
    - Hotel Ezra Cornell (Sol), 750428 (Box 15)
    - Ithaca city Officials participating in a lab session of an urban studies course, 750429 (Box 15)
    - Warren R. Philipson, Research Assoc.; Ta Liang, Professor; Dwight A. Sangrey, Assoc. Professor--all in Civil & Environmental Engineering and Campus Scenes--Andy, 750430
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Golf and Moakley House, 750431 (Box 15)
    - Steven L. Sugarman, Arts '76, Student Trustee, 750432 (Box 15)
    - Kenneth I. Greisen, Professor of Physics, Ombudsman 1975-77, 750433 (Box 15)
  - May 1975
    - Sage chapel Doord defaced (Central South Entrance (Sol), 750501 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750502 (Box 15)
    - Bruce S. Fink, Arts '77, winner of first-place award ($5,000) in "Great books of the Western World" Essay Competition, 750503
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Bob Jaffee & Rich Tiberio of the Center for Alternative Energy demonstrate a Savonius Rotor (Vertical Windmill), 750504
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - John T. Oxley Polo Arena Dedication, 750505 (Box 15)
    - Phi Psi 500--Beer-drinking race (Sol), 750506 (Box 15)
    - Infrared aerial shots depicting heat loss of campus buildings & Campus Scenes, 750507 (Box 15)
    - Physics 101 Lab, 750508 (Box 15)
    - Alumni Field, 750509 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750510 (Box 15)
    - Rrisley Fair--Jerry Edelstein '77, 750511 (Box 15)
    - Railroad Conference at ILR, Malott Hall, 750512 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750513 (Box 15)
    - Alternative Energy Exposition, 750514 (Box 15)
    - Elizabeth Komaroni, Custodian of Class of '17 Hall, Retires, 750515 (Box 15)
    - Stimson Hall Exteriors, 750516 (Box 15)
    - Final Exams, 750517 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Alumni University--Sagamore Conference Center, Racquette Lake, New York--photos by Liz Helmer, 750518 (Box 15)
    - Ed Hartz, Superintendent, Utilities; Robert H. Clawson, Utility Rate Engineer; Ben Muggeo, Mechanical Engineer look at Infrared aerial survey of Cornell Univ. Campus, 750519
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Richard T. Fauntleroy, Law '75, 750520 (Box 15)
    - Children's Vegetable Gardens, 750521 (Box 15)
  - June 1975
    - Commencement & ROTC Commissioning, 750601 (Box 15)
    - Gellman Family (Six members of immediate family graduated at Cornell), 750602 (Box 15)
    - David W. Connor, Coordinator of Religion, Ethics & Social Policy, 750603 (Box 15)
    - Presidential Councillors, 750604 (Box 15)
    - G. Michael McHugh, Director, Alumni University with abandoned young racoon, 750605 (Box 15)
    - Alumni Reunion, 750606 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750607 (Box 15)
    - Oxley Polo Arena Exteriors, 750608 (Box 15)
    - Baker Labs--Interiors & Exteriors, 750609 (Box 15)
  - July 1975
    - Isle of Shoals Marine Lab--by Wendy Zomparelli, 750701 (Box 15)
    - Summer at Cornell, 750702 (Box 15)
    - The Bullis Room in the Andrew D. White House, 750703 (Box 15)
    - Business & Public Administration--Executive Development Program, 750704 (Box 15)
    - Surplus Acquisitions Auction, 750705 (Box 15)
    - Navy vs. Cornell Lacrosse (5/75), 750706 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Alumni University Choral Group, 750707 (Box 15)
  - August 1975
    - Shoals Marine Lab-Appledore Island, 750801 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Alumni University Picnic, 750802 (Box 15)
    - Opening Ceremonies for Jr. Olympics @ Schoellkopf Field, 750803 (Box 15)
    - Photographic Equipment in Russ's Office-"S" Sticker Appeal, 750804 (Box 15)
    - Skyline Views of Cornell, 750805 (Box 15)
    - Ron Shassburger and the Wolves, 750806 (Box 15)
    - Campus Aerials, 750807 (Box 15)
    - Convocation, 750808 (Box 15)
    - Opening of Oakenshields Diningroom at Straight, 750809 (Box 15)
    - Prof. Stouffer and Shark Meat, 750810 (Box 15)
    - Mt. Pleasant Telescope; Kangaroo Rat slide copy, 750811 (Box 15)
  - September 1975
    - Soccer team in Poland, 750901 (Box 15)
    - Registration 1975 (fall), 750902 (Box 15)
    - Students repair JAPES lodge roof, 750903 (Box 15)
    - Revolutionary Dining (coop) by Liz Helmer, 750904 (Box 15)
    - Clarence Reed, new COSEP director, 750905 (Box 15)
    - Reggie Ingram - Bike Racer, 750906 (Box 15)
    - Clouds and Campus Scenes, 750907 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750908 (Box 15)
    - B & PA School - talk by William Spencer, First National City Bank President, 750909 (Box 15)
    - Dr. Evans - Vet School, 750910 (Box 15)
    - Basketball Star, Maynard Brown, 750911 (Box 15)
    - Copies of 4 old mud-rush pictures from archives, 750912 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 750913 (Box 15)
    - June Fessenden-Raden's Brown Bag Lunches with students - Day Hall, 750914 (Box 15)
    - Barbara Troxell - Voice Teacher, 750915 (Box 15)
    - Dewitt Perkins - Barn Antiques, Virgil (profile for Chronicle), 750916 (Box 15)
    - Basketball team and coaches on campus, 750917 (Box 15)
    - United Way - Cornell workers at Challenge Industries, 750918 (Box 15)
    - Margaret Stone - Bailey Hortorium, 750919 (Box 15)
    - Edward Murray - new conductor of C.U. orchestra, 750920 (Box 15)
    - Joan Davison - '48 - chairman of New York State Council on the Arts, 750921 (Box 15)
    - President Corson, 750922 (Box 15)
    - Piano (Baldwin) with Malcolm Bilson and student Claudia Hutchison, 750923 (Box 15)
    - Christening of a new shell for women's crew, 750924 (Box 15)
    - Football game - C.U. vs Colgate, 750925 (Box 15)
    - Bill Tutton, head orchard man and polo team referee - supervising apple harvest, 750926 (Box 15)
    - Aerials of campus, 750927 (Box 15)
  - October 1975
    - Jack Squire, art instructor, and his sculpture, 751001 (Box 15)
    - Patrick Filley, assistant athletic director, 751002 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751003 (Box 15)
    - Fall-In, Plantations, 751004 (Box 15)
    - Experimental solar house, 751005 (Box 15)
    - Sibley Library, 751006 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - Fall, 751007 (Box 15)
    - Vet School (Sol), 751008 (Box 15)
    - Bernard Burgunder, '18, in Rare Book room with manuscripts he has donated, 751009 (Box 15)
    - Trustee Council Meetings, 751010 (Box 15)
    - Football - C.U. vs Princeton, 751011 (Box 15)
    - Prof. McLafferty with students Henry Dayringer and Babu Venkataraghavan - with mass spectra computer system, 751012 (Box 15)
    - Art Exhibit - Thomas Armstrong and Earl Flansburgh, 751013 (Box 15)
    - Homecoming, 751014 (Box 15)
    - Joseph Silbert, '15, with Tom Leavitt looking over coin collection, 751015 (Box 15)
    - Soccer (Steve), 751016 (Box 15)
    - Pumpkin pie graph, 751017 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751018 (Box 15)
    - Hans Bethe Testimonial, 751019 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751020 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751021 (Box 15)
    - Dorm Shots (Steve), 751022 (Box 15)
    - Michael Kammen, 751023 (Box 15)
  - November 1975
    - Football game - C.U. vs Columbia, 751101 (Box 15)
    - Robert C. Walling - new director of Financial Aid, 751102 (Box 15)
    - Engineering students with Mars land roving vehicle, 751103 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751104 (Box 15)